coub.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy

All Terms Used In this COUB™ Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) unless otherwise defined herein are as defined in the COUB™ Terms of Service Agreement to which this Privacy Policy is linked and incorporated herein by reference.

* ### Introduction.

At Coub Ltd., a corporation organized under the laws of the country of Cyprus ( **“Company”** or  **“we”** ) we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to us when you sign up to use our services, including our website, Coub.com (the “Website”), our mobile applications, features or functionality and software (collectively, the “Coub Services”) and describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect:

  1. On the Coub Services

  2. In e-mail, text and other electronic messages when you use the Coub Services.

  3. When you interact with our authorized technical support partner(s) and any information and applications on third-party websites and services.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  1. us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by us or any third party; or any third party, including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from the Coub Services or on a Website.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use the Coub Services or visit the Website. By registering for or accessing our Coub Services or using the Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Coub Services or the Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates.

* ### Children Under the Age of 13.

Our Coub Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to our Coub Services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not register for any of our Coub Services or use or provide any information to the Company through our Coub Services, contribute or use any Contributions or other content generated by you as a user on the Coub Services (“User Generated Content”) , use any of the interactive or public comment features available through the Coub Services or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@coub.com](mailto:support@coub.com).

* ### Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It.

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Coub Services, including information:

  1. By which you may be personally identified, such as name, e-mail address and telephone number ( **“personally identifiable information”);**

  2. That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as the date of a user’s access to the Coub Services, or date of a Contribution of User Generated Content; and/or

  3. About your internet connection, the equipment you use, and due to the nature of mobile device applications and depending on your device settings, possibly the location of your device to access our Coub Services, and usage details.

We collect this information:

  1. Directly from you when you provide it to us, for example, upon registration for you User Account.

  2. Automatically as you navigate through the Coub Services. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.

  3. From third parties, for example, other technical support and legal copyright compliance partners.

* ### Information You Provide to Us.

The information we collect on or through our Coub Services or on a Website may include:

  1. Information that you provide by filling in forms on mobile device applications downloaded from or used to access our Coub Services. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Coub Services, subscribing to our COUB™ Products or Services, or requesting further services. For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a Coub Services User Account. When you do, we’ll ask for personally identifiable information, such as, for example, your name, email address, telephone number. And in order to take full advantage of the dynamic features we offer, we will also ask you to create a publicly visible User Profile, which may include your name and photo. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Services or Website to our User Support Team.

  2. Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us. When you contact the Company, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about the Coub Services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements.

  3. Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.

  4. Details of ownership or attribution for any User Generated Content, creative works or productions. Currently, you are not required to provide any financial information to the Company before using the Coub Services or accessing our Websites, but we reserve the right to require such information if and when we choose to offer products or services for sale through our Services or Websites.

  5. Your search queries on the Coub Services.

  6. From access through the use of a mobile computing devise such as a “smart phone”, we also may be provided and collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). This mobile device identifier information includes information such as the International Mobile Station Equipment Identity (IMEI), its WiFi radio (Media Access Control (MAC)) address and/or platform specific identifiers such as Apple®’s Advertiser ID (IDFA). Depending on the settings you have made on your mobile device, the Company may be able to associate your device identifiers or phone number with your User Account.

You may contribute User Generated Content, including photos, videos, digital media, graphics, likes or other information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, **“posted”** ) through our Coub Services, or transmitted to other users of the Coub Services or third parties. Your User Generated Content is posted and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to our Coub Services, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of our Coub Services with whom you may choose to share your User Generated Content. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Generated Content will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

* ### Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Coub Services, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  1. Details of your use of the Coub Services, including traffic data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Coub Services.

  2. Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

To the extent the information we collect automatically is intended solely to be used as statistical data, it would not be intended to identify any individual. There are instances, however, where data is collected to personalize our Coub Services to your needs, in which case data that would identify you personally could be collected. General statistical data helps us to improve our Coub Services and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:

  1. Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

  2. Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Coub Services according to your individual interests.

  3. Recognize you when you return to our Coub Services.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  1. Mobile Device Identifier’s: International Mobile Station Equipment Identity (IMEI),

  2. WiFi radio: Media Access Control (MAC)

  3. Address and/or platform specific identifiers: Apple®’s Advertiser ID (IDFA) 

  4. Google Analytics (GA)

* ### How We Use Your Information.

We use information that we collect about those authenticated users accessing our Coub Services using their mobile device, which you provide to us, including any personal information:

  1. To present our Coub Services and their content to you.

  2. To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.

  3. To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide the information.

  4. To provide you with notices about your User Account.

  5. To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

  6. To notify you about changes to our Coub Services or any products or services we offer or provide though them.

  7. To allow you to participate in interactive features in our Coub Services.

  8. In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

  9. For any other purpose with your consent.

* ### Disclosure of Your Information.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  1. To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support the Coub Services or our Website and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.

  2. To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our users of Coub Services is among the assets transferred.

  3. To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 

  4. For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

  5. With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  1. To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

  2. To enforce or apply our terms of service as set forth in the COUB™ Terms of Service Agreement and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes to the extent our Services require purchase.

  3. If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, and our users . This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection.

* ### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  1. Mobile Device Tracking Technologies and Geolocation Data.

Your mobile device may have certain settings that relate to the Applications Programming Interface or “API” that allows mobile applications or “apps” to access standard categories of content on a mobile device, but also sensitive content such as geolocation information. It is suggested by organizations responsible for the protection of consumer privacy interests, such as the Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”) that consumers should familiarize themselves with the privacy setting options available on their mobile devices to determine what information may be collected or tracked by certain applications and what steps can be taken to control that access, collection or tracking. These steps may differ depending on whether the mobile device’s operating platform is based on the “iOS” used in most Apple® smartphones or the Android™ platforms used in others. Depending on the platform used by your mobile device you should be able review the type of data collected by mobile applications, including the mobile applications provided by the Coub Services, which may vary depending on the privacy settings on your device. For further information about these privacy settings, please contact your device manufacturer, mobile service provider, or the provider of the operating platform installed on your device. For further information on data collected specific to mobile applications used for the Coub Services as provided in this Privacy Policy please contact the Company at [support@coub.com](mailto:support@coub.com).

  2. Promotional Announcements from the Company.

If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company for our own promotional announcements or events, you can opt-out by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [support@coub.com](mailto:support@coub.com). If we have sent you a promotional or event advisory e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions.

  3. We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use both personally identifiable information (e.g., your name, phone number, physical or electronic address) and non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/) or Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://networkadvertising.org/choices).

  4. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Company who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of their personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may request a list of all of the third parties with whom we share your PII by sending an e-mail to [support@coub.com](mailto:support@coub.com) and place “California Third Party Disclosure” in the subject line. Please allow up to thirty days for a response.

* ### Accessing and Correcting Your Information.

You can review and change your personal information by logging into our Coub Services and visiting your User Account page on your mobile device.

You may also send us an e-mail at [support@coub.com](mailto:support@coub.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your User Account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Generated Content from our Coub Services, copies of your User Generated Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other users of our Coub Services. Proper access and use of information provided through the Coub Services, including User Generated Content, is governed by our terms of service in the COUB™ Terms of Service Agreement.

* ### Privacy When Linking To Social Networking Sites.

When you associate a Social Networking Site such as Facebook or Twitter (“SNS”) with the Coub Services during either account registration or account linking, you allow the Company to access certain personal and non-personal information that you provided to each respective SNS, such as your user ID, first and last name, profile picture, email address and associated usage data. By accessing our Coub Services through an SNS, you are authorizing the Company to collect, store and use all information that you agreed the SNS could provide to the Company through the SNS. The Company’s collection, storage and use of your information are governed by this Privacy Policy.

* ### Your California Privacy Rights.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Coub Services that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [support@coub.com](mailto:support@coub.com).

* ### Data Security.

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any User Account information will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of the Coub Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted through our Coub Services. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained in our Coub Services.

* ### Changes to Our Privacy Policy.

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Coub™ Privacy Policy link on the Website, or the Privacy Policy link in our Coub Services to review this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

* ### Contact Information.

To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [support@coub.com](mailto:support@coub.com).
